And today is the,
but the day didn't start like that.
After I got over this whole bank conflict,
I decided to invest in an idea.
This tire here,
oh,
at least it doesn't get so crooked,
is it on?
Juninho will help me get the bank out,
go Juninho
caraca, bro.
Biggest space left,
huh?
Dad, look,
if you want change in your life,
start taking action.
See,
Vay evladım kalıyo.
Weird a little when he rips off the bank,
right?
I went,
went in reverse,
put my little hand in here to look.
I'm in the biggest here,
man,
because I don't know if I USE this space I just created for
ME to sleep OR if I set up something profitable in this space.
It's on here,
not the bank.
I took the step back there.
Oh,
but where I put these,
they can screw and lock.
The idea is good,
O Caio.
You have to be more daring to be able to conquer things.
Vei,
otherwise it's asking for a tape measure to measure this space here,
o
You don't want me to love you
space here old i can use it for me to sleep,
put a board so bro i can stretch smooth bro
look at my foot here i sleep well bro well class a
hi helvete
bye bye
haha
i wanna be your back.